Pajar

Full Stack Developer

+62 896-1616-4757

pajarmaulana190@gmail.com

Bogor, Indonesia

pajar-portofolio.netlify.app



About me

Junior programmer with 1+ years of experience using Javascript and PHP frameworks to develop, test and observe software applications and servers in a company. Have created and developed more than 5 applications for efficiency and record keeping for the Indonesian Ministry of Health (Kemenkes) and the National Disaster Management Agency (BNPB). Interested in Fullstack Developer, Backend Developer and System Analyst positions.

Experience

Full Stack Developer

PT Zamasco Mitra Solusindo

Jul 2023 - Mar 2024

- Resolved debugs and implemented new solutions for Ministry of Health (Kementrian Kesehatan) and BNPB applications
- Improve effectiveness for the use of attendance through the Absensi application
- Design a Warehouse Management System (WMS) for BNP logistics needs
- Designing and creating a website for recording votes during elections for the Gelora Party

Backend Developer Intern

PT Immobi Solusi Prima

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023

- Create and develop the company's Task Management application
- Improve the performance of each feature in the company's ERP application
- Testing the program and discussing with the team for the effectiveness of the application

Education

2020-2023

Wikrama Vocational High School

Software Engineer

Tech Stack





Nginx



Hard Skill

Web Development

Data Analyst

Testing and Debuging

Soft Skill

Adaptability and Flexibility

Critical Thinking

Teamwork

Problem Solving